Faculty Handbooks; Collection ua938
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Faculty Handbooks Collection
1948-1994
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany
ua938
0.8 cubic ft.
This collection is made up of faculty handbooks for professors at the University of Albany.
Historical Note
The first Faculty Handbook was created in 1948 as guidance for new teachers at the New York State College for Teachers. The handbook was published until the 1990s, serving professors who would also work at the newly relocated and renamed State University of New York at Albany.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains faculty handbooks printed between 1948 and 1994. They contain information related t how profesors should conduct themselves in the classroom, as well as Univeristy protocol on dealing with students.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into chronological order.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Handbooks, vade-mecums, etc.; Universities and colleges--Faculty; UAlbany Reference Collections
- Faculty Handbook, 1948 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 1)
- Faculty Handbook, 1952 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 1)
- Faculty Handbook, 1963 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 1)
- Faculty Handbook, 1966 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 1)
- Faculty Handbook, 1966 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 1)
- Faculty Handbook, 1966 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 2)
- Faculty Handbook, 1966 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 2)
- Faculty Handbook, 1967 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 2)
- Faculty Handbook, 1968 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 2)
- Faculty Handbook, 1969 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 2)
- Faculty Handbook, 1970 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 2)
- Faculty Handbook, 1971 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 2)
- Faculty Handbook, 1972 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 3)
- Faculty Handbook, 1973 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 3)
- Faculty Handbook, 1974 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 3)
- Faculty Handbook, 1974 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 3)
- Faculty Handbook, 1975 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 4)
- Faculty Handbook, 1976 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 4)
- Faculty Handbook, 1977 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 4)
- Faculty Handbook, 1978 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 4)
- Faculty Handbook, 1979 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 4)
- Faculty Handbook, 1980 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 5)
- Faculty Handbook, 1980 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 5)
- Faculty Handbook, 1981 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 5)
- Faculty Handbook, 1982 (Box 1 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 5)
- Faculty Handbook, 1984 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 1)
- Faculty Handbook, 1984 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 1)
- Faculty Handbook, 1984 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 1)
- Faculty Handbook, 1985 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 2)
- Faculty Handbook, 1986 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 3)
- Faculty Handbook, 1986 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 3)
- Faculty Handbook, 1987 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 3)
- Faculty Handbook, 1989 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 4)
- Faculty Handbook, 1989 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 4)
- Faculty Handbook, 1989 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 4)
- Faculty Handbook, 1990 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 5)
- Faculty Handbook, 1990 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 5)
- Faculty Handbook, 1990 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 5)
- Faculty Handbook, 1990 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 5)
- Faculty Handbook, 1992 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 6)
- Faculty Handbook, 1992 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 6)
- Faculty Handbook, 1994 (Box 2 (Faculty Handbooks Collection), Folder 7)